<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Driving Cars on InfoTrendSpot</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/self-driving-cars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Driving Cars on InfoTrendSpot</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/self-driving-cars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Electric Vehicles: Latest Models and Innovations</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/latest-electric-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/latest-electric-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Electric Vehicles (EVs) have changed and improved from the beginning. EVs are more popular now due to their positive response to the environment and new improved technologies. These technologies are safe for humans as well as other species. This article looks at how EVs started, the latest models in this category, and new upcoming features.&#xA;Starting of EVs&#xD;First Electric Vehicle was made in the 1800s. EVs didn&amp;rsquo;t become popular in those days because their weak batteries and gas cars took over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Safety Project Launched For Self-Driving Cars</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/safety-project-launched-self-driving-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/safety-project-launched-self-driving-cars/</guid>
      <description>The scientists and experts from the University of Surrey has started a new plan to make the self-driving cars journey more safe and secure. Interior view of a self-driving car About the project:&#xD;They named this safety project Massdrive, this project is set to revolutionize the approval and certification process for autonomous vehicles, ensuring their safety and reliability as they hit the roads.&#xA;Professor Saber Fallah a key figure in the project, says they want to work together with car makers, rule setters, teachers, government people, and local communities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
