<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on InfoTrendSpot</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on InfoTrendSpot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Cybersecurity: Advanced Threat Detection and Automated Response in 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ai-for-cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ai-for-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>In the high pace and dynamism of the world of cybersecurity, AI proves itself very handy for the fight against evolved cyber threats. Integration of technologies AI and ML therefore makes security measures proactive, further easing threat detection and early mitigation.&#xA;AI-Enabled Threat Detection and Response AI and ML do make cybersecurity better, as the text is correct: they analyze vast amounts of data almost in real-time so as to be able to single out any signals concerning a security breach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are major cyber attack factors and how to stay safe from cyber-attacks?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cyber-attack-factors-and-save-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cyber-attack-factors-and-save-techniques/</guid>
      <description>A lot of companies and organizations were attacked by cyber criminals, today we&amp;rsquo;ll see some common and major techniques used in cyber attacks and how to stay safe from getting an attack.&#xA;Human Error It&amp;rsquo;s a very common mistake we often make. We click on malicious links, or we use easy-to-guess passwords. Hackers can get personal data with these little mistakes. We should use strong passwords which contains alphabets, nubmer, and symbols that can&amp;rsquo;t be accessed very easily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forcepoint Automatic Data Protection on Risky Behavior - A Tour to Forcepoint DLP Protection </title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/forcepoint-automatic-date-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/forcepoint-automatic-date-protection/</guid>
      <description>In the developing world of cybersecurity, the needs for safe and secure landscape to finalize frauds of fraudsters is paramount. Traditional data loss prevention(DLP) strategies often fails in addressing the dynamic nature of risks, which cause defenceless or unprotected atmosphere to your company. However, a new automatic cyber defense system by Forcepoint is very beneficial under these circumstances.&#xA;Real-Time Response to Evolving Risks Rapid pace is one of the major callange in data security at which risks can terminate and come to an end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell CyberSense for Empowring Your Digital Defense</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/dell-cybersense/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/dell-cybersense/</guid>
      <description>In today’s world of business, keeping data safe is main priority. But, there’s a big problem: lots of companies have been attacked by cybercriminals who stop them from getting to their data. What’s even scarier is that many of these companies don’t feel sure they can recover if this happens. But, there’s some good news in the fight against these cybercriminals – it comes in the form of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
